raptmedia.com 2019-07-06

# Privacy Policy - Rapt Media

### I. Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy states what information Rapt Media, Inc. (“Rapt Media”) collects from users of its RAPTMEDIA.COM website (the “Site”), RAPT MEDIA interactive video engineering platform, and associated analytics services (the platform and analytics services, collectively the “Services”), and how this information is used. Your use of the Site, Services and/or registration on the Site constitutes acceptance by you of the terms of this Privacy Policy. Any changes to Rapt Media’s Privacy Policy will be effective when posted. Your continued use of this Site and/or Services following the posting of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance to those changes.

### II. Information Collected

Depending on how you access the Site and Services, Rapt Media may collect personal information through the Site in connection with your user registration on the Site, including contact information such as your first and last name, your mailing address, your telephone number and your e-mail addresses. We use this information to send our users information about our Site and to contact the user when necessary. From time to time, Rapt Media or its business affiliates may also use your registration information to send you offers and promotions that may be of interest to you. By providing your contact information, you give us permission to send you such materials. Users may opt-out of receiving certain future mailings. See the choice/opt-out section below. In addition, when you pay fees via the Site, we will collect personal information through your payment method (e.g., credit card, debit card, or other payment method accepted by Rapt Media) We use your credit card or other billing information to obtain payment for registration or other Services you have purchased.

We also receive and store certain types of information whenever you access the Site. We may set and access cookies on your computer and use web beacons, clear GIFs or pixel tags to provide us with information about your browsing experience.  
As you use our Site and/or the Services, we may collect and store IP addresses, the website address that brought you to our Site, the website address where videos you create using our Services are displayed, the interactions with those videos, including the website address to which each viewer goes when they stop viewing such videos, the video viewing duration and the number of times each video is viewed.

We use the information collected to deliver the Services, help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Site and/or Services, as well as to save your password so you don’t have to reenter it each time you visit our Site.  
If you prefer not to accept cookies, you can set your browser to reject them or to alert you before one is placed on your computer. Note that some features of our Site may not be available if you do not accept cookies.

### III. Sharing of Information

Rapt Media may release personal information when we: (1) respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, and we exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (2) believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Terms of Service or as otherwise required by law; or (3) transfer information about you if Rapt Media is acquired by or merged with another entity.

### IV. Choice/Opt-Out

Each email communication sent from Rapt Media to you provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future communications from Rapt Media. Please allow up to 45 days for your opt-out request to take effect.

### V. Links to Other Websites

The Site contains links to other websites. Rapt Media does not control the privacy policies of business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other websites to which Rapt Media provides hyperlinks.

### VI. Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of the Rapt Media who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to info@Rapt Media.com or write us:

Rapt Media, Inc.  
1401 Walnut St. Suite #200  
Boulder, CO 80302
